Welcome to CL Enterprises.  Guys in today's
video we will learn how to close Money View Loan
?  To close a Money View Loan, the
terms and conditions have to be
followed.  If you have
taken a loan from Money View for six months.  The maximum
tenure is six months, so you
cannot foreclose the loan.  You are
not allowed.  The tenure ranges from 7 months to 18 months.
So
the option becomes available after six EMIs are paid.
Friends, if you have taken a loan for a tenure of more than 18 months, then
you will have to pay
12 installments and then you can
close it.  So you have to fulfill this condition.
Apart from these, friends,
if you have taken a loan from Money View, its
installment six is ​​still pending.
Your loan will be closed as soon as six EMIs are completed.
So even in such a situation you cannot do fore close.
This option is available in your Money View app if you follow the terms and conditions.  You
can close your loan by paying your outstanding due amount.  So first
you have to open the Money View app.  When you
login to the Money app, the
home interface of Money View becomes available to you.   The
amount of loan you have taken from Moneyview will be shown here.
Friends, we had earlier applied for a loan of Rs 45,000 for
24 months.
We have paid more than 12 installments.  So simply
we have to click on loan.  As soon as
friends click on loan, we
come to this page.  Here
you can see the loan overview on the top side.
How much loan did you take?  How much is the installment?
You can see the loan ID.  The date on which
your installment is debited is
also mentioned here.
By clicking on View EMI Details, you can see
how much EMI is remaining.  How much EMI you have to pay to
close the loan.
Friends, we have to pay the estimated seven EMIs now.
Then our loan will be closed.  We
close this loan in advance.  So
for this, simply friends,
you get the option of three lines on the top side.  You have to click on this.
As soon as friends
click on the three lines, the payment
details open in front of you.  In the payment details,
you can see that our overdue EMI has
increased by 1 day.  So the amount is being given in overdue.  There are
zero pending penalties here.
You can see the outstanding principal and the interest for 1
day has been added here.
Foreclosure charges are zero here.
Because friends Money View
provides us loan at floating rate.  According to RBI guidelines,
all floating rate
loans are foreclosed.  So no
charges are taken from us.
You can see the total loan amount.
You will be able to see here below how much we have to pay in total.
After that click on Pay Now.
As soon as friends click on Pay Now,
you are redirected
to this page.  There
are three options available for you to make the payment.  Debit Card,
UPI and Net Banking.  Friends, we will
use UPI here.  PhonePe,
Google P, Paytm.  You
can use any UPI.  So, here we have
debited the payment through PhonePe.
We have
successfully debited the payment here through PhonePe.
So you can see this kind of
interface comes up.  After the payment is made, the
EMI paid option becomes available to you.
Friends, if you visit the home page
, whatever loan
was pending here is not shown.   It
comes under closed loan.  If you want, you
can download its statement.  Its
NOC is sent to your registered email.
For NOC request
you have to mail to different landing
partners.  The mail ID is different.  So for this
you simply open the app.
Click on the three lines.  Here you will simply
click on Help and Support.
Visit Personal Loan.  Click on NOC.  If you
click on NOC, you
get an email ID here within seconds.
You will have to mail on that for NOC.
Because friends, there are different landing
partners here.  So
you will have to mail according to which landing partner you have here.
NOC is also provided to you within 15 days.  This
is a simple process friends.  If you have
applied for a loan from Money View and your
requirement has been fulfilled, then you
can close the loan.  Whatever
is your outstanding due amount, you have to pay it
so that you are not required to pay
extra interest on any pending EMI in future.
If you liked the video, please give it a like.
Share it with your friends
and subscribe to our channel clerpries
so that you
get information about such videos first.